<posts>
    <post>
        <title>Pale Shadow</title>
        <subtitle> [To You & To Me] </subtitle>
        <body>
            
I am sorry the words have not flowed easily out of my mouth and rested nicely in the grooves of conversation. 

Cradle soft the private woman I have become out of practice. 


Unable to see the face, I see glimpses, in retrospect, in your face now that appears to me as I write this. 

Pale shadows, the muted pinks of my body will not apologize for the indifference of this stage. It must surely play out visibly in that body as it stumbles. 

Why must you fall with your head first and your eyes open? I shout back at you -


my theater - your theater.


Filled with perfect teeth that bite heels, I prefer my tongue as it was given to me. 

I will perform when I want to bleed. 


Yet, I have not balanced on these feet and I am scared. I don't like rooms like this, or people like you, so tell me. Honestly and without pity bearing the silence of obligation. 


I don't want to know because I know. I want to know because you tell me. 


So I can move town with the circus and embarrass with no audience. 
            
        </body>
        <body-second>
        </body-second>
        <date>7-1-2025</date>
        <image>one.png</image>
    </post>
    <post>
        <title>Lotus in the Rain</title>
        <subtitle>The Calm</subtitle>
        <body>
        I found this piece the other day and couldn’t stop staring at it. A lotus, blooming under the relentless fall of rain — delicate, fragile, but undeniably strong. The colors are wild. A muted storm of blue dots forms the flower and the sky, while two bold red panels interrupt everything — like symbols dropped in from a different world. One spiral pulls you in, the other swirls with clouds, a snake, and blossoms.
        </body>
        <body-second>
        I didn’t expect to get hit by something as simple as an image today, but here we are. Sometimes the right thing finds you exactly when it should.
        </body-second>
        <date>2025-06-19</date>
        <image>cool.jpg</image>
    </post>
</posts>
