<posts>
    <post>
        <title>Pale Shadow</title>
        <subtitle> [To You &amp; To Me] </subtitle>
        <body>
            I am sorry the words have not flowed easily out of my mouth and rested nicely in the grooves of conversation. 

            Cradle soft the private woman I have become out of practice. 


            Unable to see the face, I see glimpses, in retrospect, in your face now that appears to me as I write this. 

            Pale shadows, the muted pinks of my body will not apologize for the indifference of this stage. It must surely play out visibly in that body as it stumbles. 

            Why must you fall with your head first and your eyes open? I shout back at you -


            my theater - your theater.


            Filled with perfect teeth that bite heels, I prefer my tongue as it was given to me. 

            I will perform when I want to bleed. 


            Yet, I have not balanced on these feet and I am scared. I don't like rooms like this, or people like you, so tell me. Honestly and without pity bearing the silence of obligation. 


            I don't want to know because I know. I want to know because you tell me. 


            So I can move town with the circus and embarrass with no audience. 
            
        </body>
        <body-second>
        </body-second>
        <date>7-1-2025</date>
        <image>one.png</image>
    </post>

    <post>
        <title>Lady Cardinal</title>
        <subtitle> [I wear clothes even when I'm dreaming] </subtitle>
        <body>
The gentle movement of the needle 
Like water through worn seams.

My mother’s dress 
Lived permanently.

Sunken deep 
I watched her muscles stretch. 
 
Giving no ground
As the clock echoed her breath.

I did not speak.

She would let me stay 
With my bony knees 
Pressed against my chin
And my hands under my feet. 


The cardinal had much to say, 

so I listened. 

If there was more to me then,
I couldn't find it.
        </body>
        <body-second>
        </body-second>
        <date>7-3-2025</date>
        <image>two.png</image>
        
    </post>
    
     <post>
        <title>Dead End Exits</title>
        <subtitle> [Time eats away with me] </subtitle>
        <body>
There is an icebox somewhere still with your name on it.
 
There was a puddle in my lap in the backseat, so you screamed at me. 

I have yet to see proof that we came here. A cop trailed us then too.
            
My eyes stared at the truck carrying empty cages through dead end exits.

I didn’t look when you threw, or when it hit ground.
Just the same as I don’t care to look now.

In the rear view, he takes the same turn that we took.
My lips are blue like the icebox, perhaps it wouldn’t be there if I looked.
        </body>
        <body-second>
        </body-second>
        <date>7-23-2025</date>
        <image>four.png</image>
        
    </post>
</posts>
